A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, officers' diaries, RG 12, S-Z FA394
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Willits, Joseph H., 0.58 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box, 1 half-letter document box, and 1 microfilm box (35mm)
  - Exhibits, 1943-1946; Willits, Joseph H. (Joseph Henry) (1889-1979); Rockefeller Foundation. Division of Social Sciences
    United States; Social sciences
- Wilson, David B., 0.85 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box and 1 legal document box
  - 1932 January-May (Box 525)
  - 1932 June-December (Box 525)
  - 1934 (Box 525)
  - 1937-1938 (Box 525)
  - 1939-1941 (Box 526)
  - 1940, 1944, 1948, 1950-1951 (Box 526)
- Winegar, Elizabeth A., 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - 1961-1962 (Box 526)
  - 1963 (Box 526)
- Wing, Wilson Mumford, 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  - 1947-1948 (Box 526)
- Wood, Peter H., 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - 1971-1972 (Box 527)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 527)
- Work, Telford Hindley, 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - 1953-1956 (Box 527)
- Worth, C. Brooke, 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  Mexico; Philippines
  - 1947-1953 (Box 527)
- Wortman, L. Sterling, 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - 1966 January-May (Box 528)
  - 1966 June-December (Box 528)
  - 1967 (Box 528)
  - 1968 (Box 529)
  - 1969 (Box 529)
  - 1970 (Box 530)
  - 1971 (Box 530)
  - 1972 (Box 530)
  - 1973 (Box 531)
  - 1974 (Box 531)
  - 1975 (Box 531)
  - Index, 1966-1974 (Box 531)
- Wray, Joe D., 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - 1961 (Box 532)
  - 1962 (Box 532)
  - 1963 (Box 532)
  - 1964 (Box 532)
  - 1965-1968, 1971, 1973 (Box 532)
- Wright, Bill C., 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - 1968-1969 (Box 533)
- Wright, Christopher, 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - 1972-1973 (Box 533)
- Young, Geoffrey Winthrop, 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - 1929-1930 (Box 533)
- Yudelman, Montague, 0.95 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes and 1 half-letter document box
  - 1956 (Box 533)
  - 1957 (Box 534)
  - 1958 (Box 534)
  - 1959 (Box 535)
- Zinn, Earl F., 0.19 Cubic Feet 1 half-letter document box
  - 1926-1927 (Box 535)